CAMERON MALFARA

A Retail Customer Service Representative with four years of experience, specializing in customer support, client relations, sales management, and communication. A strong history of interfacing with a broad range of customers to identify appropriate solutions and ensure satisfaction.

123 Bedford Avenue, New York, NY, 12345 earner on ma I fa ra@ exa m p le.com (123) 456-7890

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

RETAIL CUSTOMER SERVICE ASSOCIATE

BestBuy, New York, NY October 2019- Present

- Provide support to 25-35 customers per day, educate customers on electronics, payment plans, and rewards programs, and exceed monthly sales goals by 30%-40%
- Identify solutions to customer issues, including defective products, refunds, store
 c red it, and ac h i eve customer sa ti sfaction rati n gs of 91%-94% YOY
- Coordinate with a team of 20+ retail sales and customer service associates to reduce customer wait times, identify appropriate solutions, and enhance daily operations

RETAIL CUSTOMER SERVICE ASSOCIATE

Target, New York, NY June 2018 -October 2019

- Responded to phone calls and in-store inquiries from retail customers, guided shoppers in locating productsand merchandise,and communicated with empathy and understanding
- Communicated with other local stores and departments to aid customers,
 resulting in a 91% customer service ranking over 12 consecutive months

EDUCATION

High School Diploma

Central Park East High School. New York, NY September 2014- June 2018

KEY SKILLS

- ♦ Reta i I Cu sto mer Service
- ♦ Communication
- ♦ Sales
- ♦ Upselling
- ♦ Process Improvement